

Implication is a molcay in the molcay in th

Summary_

I'm a Software Engineer mostly focused on Python at EPAM Systems Poland. I have **6+ years** of experience specialising in **full-stack web development**, and I have experience with different cloud providers like **Amazon Web Services (AWS)** and **Google Cloud Platform (GCP)**. I love ***nix based environments** and enjoy customising all of the development cycles and automating stuff. Also, I am interested in devising better **problem-solving methods** for challenging tasks and **learning new technologies**.

Skills

Programming Python, JavaScript, Java, Scala

WebDjango, Vue.js, React, Play, Flask, SpringOthersLinux, Docker, GCP, AWS, Bash, Jenkins

Languages Turkish, English

Work Experience ____

EPAM System, Project BKraków, POLAND

SOFTWARE ENGINEER January 2024 - Present

· Worked for an one of the FAANG company

• Part of a team contributes the Apache Airflow

Tech stack: Python, Docker

• Contributed to a team develops a Cloud-base product of the customer

Tech stack: Django (Python), Docker

EPAM System, Project A

Kraków, POLAND

SOFTWARE ENGINEER November 2021 - December 2023

• Worked for an HR and Workforce Management Solution company

• Contributed to a team develops a chatbot for the companies various products

Tech stack: aiohttp (Python), Socket.io for Python (WebSocket), Docker

• Contributed a team develops a tool to manage HR tasks

Tech stack: Django (Python), Docker

Urla Digital Agriculture

Urla, İzmir, TURKEY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

June 2020 - October 2021

• Developed software and the hybrid infrastructure for IoT devices (Raspberry Pi) that automate the controlled-environment agriculture **Tech stack:** Python, Docker, Amazon Web Services (like Lambda, RDS, SQS, SNS, DynamoDB, S3, Timestream, Kinesis Firehose)

• Developed a dashboard to configure, update, and control IoT devices (Raspberry Pi) remotely

Tech stack: Django (Python), MySQL, SQLite, Docker

Linovi Urla, İzmir, TURKEY

SOFTWARE ENGINEER December 2017 - June 2020

• Developed and maintained web services that serve as chatbots (Jira, Asana, GitHub, Zendesk, Salesforce, Pagerduty) for Google Chat. **Tech stack:** Play (Scala), React (Javascript), MySQL, Redis, Jenkins, Google Cloud Platform (like AppEngine, Compute Engine, Cloud Pub/Sub)

Developed a dashboard for an autonomous driving software company

Tech stack: Vert.x (Java), React (JavaScript), Amazon Web Services

• Contributed a Software as a Service called Asena for an information security firm

Tech stack: Spring (Java), Angular.js (JavaScript), Flask (Python), Redmine

Education & Certificates

EDUCATION

Muğla Sıtkı Koçman University

Muğla, TURKEY

COMPUTER ENGINEERING GPA: 3.52 / 4.00

September 2012 - June 2017

FEBRUARY 29, 2024 OLCAY TERCANLI · RÉSUMÉ